french-games.net 2017-09-16

# Free MFL Language teaching and learning resources online

### Key details

This website privacy policy describes how iclanguage ltd protects and makes use of the information you give the company when you use this website.

If you are asked to provide information when using this website, it will only be used in the ways described in this privacy policy.

This policy is updated from time to time. The latest version is published on this page.

This website privacy policy was updated on 09 September 2014.

If you have any questions about this policy, you can email us using the details on our contacts page or write to: iclanguage ltd, 24 Clifton Street, Aberdare, RCT CF44 7PB, UK.

**We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties**

### Introduction

We gather and use certain information about individuals in order to provide products and services and to enable certain functions on this website.

We also collect information to better understand how visitors use this website and to present timely, relevant information to them.

### What data we gather

We may collect the following information:

  * Name and job title
  * Contact information including email address
  * Demographic information, such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * Website usage data

### How we use this data

Collecting this data helps us understand what you are looking from the company, enabling us to deliver improved products and services.

Specifically, we may use data:

  * For our own internal records
  * To improve the products and services we provide
  * To contact you in response to a specific enquiry
  * To customise the website for you
  * To send you promotional emails about products, services, offers and other things we think might be relevant to you.

### Cookies and how we use them

#### What is a cookie?

A cookie is a small file placed on your computer's hard drive. It enables our websites to identify your computer as you view different pages on our websites.

Cookies allow websites and applications to store your preferences in order to present content, options or functions that are specific to you. They also enable us to see information like how many people use the website and what pages they tend to visit. 

#### How we use cookies

We may use cookies to:

  * **Analyse our web traffic using an analytics package.** Aggregated usage data helps us improve the website structure, design, content and functions.
  *  **Identify whether you are signed in to our website.** A cookie allows us to check whether you are signed in to the site.
  * **Test content on our website.** For example, 50% of our users might see one piece of content, the other 50% a different piece of content.
  * **Store information about your preferences.** The website can then present you with information you will find more relevant and interesting.
  * **To recognise when you return to our website.** We may show your relevant content, or provide functionality you used previously.

Cookies do not provide us with access to your computer or any information about you, other than that which you choose to share with us. 

#### Controlling cookies

You can use your web browser’s cookie settings to determine how our website uses cookies. If you do not want our website to store cookies on your computer or device, you should set your web browser to refuse cookies.

However, please note that doing this may affect how our website functions. Some pages and services may become unavailable to you.

Unless you have changed your browser to refuse cookies, our website will issue cookies when you visit it.

To learn more about cookies and how they are used, visit [All About Cookies](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

### Controlling information about you

We will never lease, distribute or sell your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or the law requires us to.

Any personal information we hold about you is stored and processed under our data protection policy, in line with the Data Protection Act 1998.

### Security

We will always hold your information securely.

To prevent unauthorised disclosure or access to your information, we have implemented strong physical and electronic security safeguards. We also follow stringent procedures to ensure we work with all personal data in line with the Data Protection Act 1998. 

### Payment Flow and Delivery Policy

All services sold on this site are subscription packages allowing access to otherwise restricted areas of the website. Following payment in full, access to these areas is immediate and persists for the duration of the subscription purchased. All subscriptions renew automatically. 

### Refund/Cancelation Policy

All subscription products can be assessed beforehand by taking advantage of our free teaching packages. You may cancel your subscription and receive a full refund up to 7 days from starting that subscription. Please contact us by eMail to cancel a subscription. The eMail address can be found on our Contacts page.

All subscriptions renew automatically. Cancel a subscription by sending an eMail to iclanguage before the subscription period expires.

### Links from our site

Our website may contain links to other websites.

Please note that we have no control of websites outside the iclanguage.com domain. If you provide information to a website to which we link, we are not responsible for its protection and privacy.

Always be wary when submitting data to websites. Read the site’s data protection and privacy policies fully.

back to top

## Privacy Policy for our Kids Applications

This Privacy Policy describes the information collected by ic language ltd through our kid mobile applications which as of today are only our two Preschool English ClickIn applications (the free version and the paid vesion).

We don't collect any personal data with our kid applications. We don't require you to provide any information when using our kid's apps and we don't collect, share or use any information about you or your device.

If you submit a support request via e-mail, we will receive your email address and other information you provide related to your support request. We use this information only to provide support to you. We don't share your email address unless you ask us to.

  1. Our kids apps don't use or collect a user's geographic location.
  2. Our kids apps don't contain any advertising but they may contain information about our other kids apps with links to those other ic language kids apps.
  3. Our kids apps don't contain any external links.
  4. Our kids apps don't store any cookies or other information retaining technologies on any device.

If you have any questions regarding this policy please email us: info (at) iclanguage.com.

back to top

Copyright iclanguage ltd 2017 : all rights reserved
